Guide to the James B. Hunt Papers
James B. Hunt Papers
- Audiotape, 1976, 1983-1984, 1990-1992, 1996, and undated
  - BRT Luncheon Remarks, Education/Skills training workshop, 1992 June 4 (Box 50)
  - Internal Medicine Interview, 1992 June 29 (Box 50)
  - 60 sec Bio Gardner (Part II of II), 1992 July 7 (Box 50)
  - Gardner Radio Biography Ad, I of II, 1992 July 7 (Box 50)
  - Wilkes County Regional Fundraiser / Governor's School, 1992 July 8 (Box 50)
  - Winston-Salem "Citizen's Forum" / Salem College Speech, 1992 July 9 (Box 50)
  - Salem College Speech (Continued) / WSJS Call-in, 1992 July 9 (Box 50)
  - Hunt Attacked on Taxes / (North Carolina Republican Party) WPTF and the Southern Farm Network, 1992 July 13 (Box 50)
  - Hawke Press Conference Taxes, 1992 July 17 (Box 50)
  - Day 139 Senate Chamber (Gardner's Last Remarks to Senate), 1992 July 24 (Box 50)
  - North Carolina GOP Attack - Hunt Attacked on Education Bureaucracy, 1992 July 28 (Box 50)
  - Jim Gardner the Big Stinker Press Conference, Outside the Hall of Justice, Winston-Salem - With Love From Kiki, 1992 August 7 (Box 50)
  - Education Bureaucracy Radio Ad / Television Audio 1st Tax Ad/ Gardner Attack - 2nd Tax Ad on Hunt, 1992 August 24 (Box 50)
  - Charlotte Observer Interview on Lobbying, 1992 August 26 (Box 50)
  - NARAL Endorsement Press Conference, Hunt, 1992 August 31 (Box 50)
  - Gardner Economic Plan Press Conference, 1992 August 31 (Box 50)
  - Debate - State Employees; Gardner Comments after Debate to Press, 1992 September 10 (Box 50)
  - Sheriff's Endorsement Press Conference, 1992 September 14 (Box 50)
  - Hunt Day Care Press Conference, 1992 September 17 (Box 50)
  - JH-03R, "Plan 3" (Radio), 1992 September 19 (Box 50)
  - 100 Day Plan / Action Agenda Press Conferences, 1992 September 21 (Box 50)
  - News & Observer Issue Series Interview, 1992 September 24 (Box 50)
  - NC Association of Broadcasters Debate (Part I), 1992 September 27 (Box 50)
  - NC Association of Broadcasters Debate (Part II), 1992 September 27 (Box 50)
  - Hunt/Gardner Comments after NC Association of Broadcasters Debate, 1992 September 27 (Box 50)
  - WUNC Interview, 1992 September 28 (Box 50)
  - ACT DOT interview, 1992 September 29 (Box 50)
  - Gardner Radio Ad, Education Record Attack, 1992 September 29 (Box 50)
  - JH-04R, "Fair;" JH-05R, "Educate", 1992 September 30 (Box 50)
  - JH-04R, "Fair;" JH-05R, "Educate", 1992 September 30 (Box 50)
  - Gardner, Greensboro YMCA, Debate Truth, 1992 September 30 (Box 50)
  - Open Net call-in, 1992 October 1 (Box 50)
  - Gardner Education Press Conference, 1992 October 2 (Box 50)
  - Dennis Whittington Interview, Business NC, 1992 October 5 (Box 50)
  - JA-03R, "Plan 3" :60R, Citizens for Jim Hunt, 1992 October 5 (Box 50)
  - JA-03R, "Plan 3", 1992 October 5 (Box 50)
  - Lobbyist / Radio 60 sec, 1992 October 6 (Box 50)
  - JH-06R, "Trust", 1992 October 8 (Box 50)
  - JH-06R, "Trust", 1992 October 8 (Box 50)
  - Drug Cabinet Press Conference, 1992 October 16 (Box 50)
  - Hunt: "Dream" w/Music, "Dream" W/Gospel Music, 1992 October 19 (Box 50)
  - JH-07R, "Dream", 1992 October 19 (Box 50)
  - JH-07R, "Dream", 1992 October 19 (Box 50)
  - JH-08R, "News", 1992 October 19 (Box 50)
  - JH-08R, "News", 1992 October 19 (Box 50)
  - JH-09R, "Attend", 1992 October 19 (Box 50)
  - JH-09R, "Attend", 1992 October 19 (Box 50)
  - Hunt: "Dream" w/Music, "Dream" W/Gospel Music, 1992 October 19 (Box 50)
  - JH-10R. "Hamlet", 1992 October 20 (Box 50)
  - State Government Paper / WSOC Forum, 1992 October 20 (Box 50)
  - JH-11R, "Difference", 1992 October 30 (Box 50)
  - JH-11R, "Difference", 1992 October 1992 (Box 50)
  - Hunt for Governor: "Utilities," "Jobs/Students," "Schools," "Tight Fisted," "People," "Crime", 1992 (Box 49)
  - Jim Hunt for Governor: Tobacco #1, #2, #3, 1992 (Box 49)
  - North Carolina for Budget Responsibility: NCB96-01R"Veto" rough mix, 1996 October 21 (Box 49)
  - Citizens for Jim Hunt: JH96-04R, "Agenda", 1996 October 24 (Box 49)
  - North Carolinians for Budget Responsibility: NCB96-02R, "Generic Veto", 1996 October 25 (Box 49)
  - Dedication Ceremony - Lineberry Criminal Justice Denter - Davidson Community College / June 14 - Women's Caucus, Meredith, 1996 (Box 50)
  - Gantt for Hunt, undated (Box 49)
  - Hunt disclaimer, undated (Box 49)
  - Hunt: JHSEN 1037, "Young or Old", undated (Box 49)
  - Jimmy Phillips, undated (Box 49)
  - The Jim Hunt Committee: That's Enough For Me, undated (Box 49)
  - Voter Reg. - Gantt, undated (Box 49)
  - Hunt - All Approved Spots, undated (Box 49)
  - Hunt/Crime Neg, Helms for Senate, 8/8 - TFN, undated (Box 49)
  - Black + Utilities + Fired, undated (Box 49)
  - Carter/King, Sr., undated (Box 49)
  - Demo Ex. Committee Hunt/Hoke, undated (Box 49)
  - Jim Hunt for Governor: 5 :30 radio spots, undated (Box 49)
  - Jim Hunt for Governor: Good News * Our Jim Hunt * Sing for Jim * Governor Hunt * Step to the Rear, undated (Box 49)
  - Side 1: Jim Hunt Spots; Side 2: [illegible] Blues, undated (Box 49)
  - DHS Films, Roberta Flack - Voter Registration, undated (Box 50)
  - JHSEN-1019, "Griffith-Smile", undated (Box 50)
  - Taxes Press Conference Radio Feed (Tape 3), undated (Box 50)
  - WUNC Radio Roundtable on Alleged Phone Tapping, WPTF 680 AM "Investigated", undated (Box 50)
  - Democratic Party Radio 5 60 second commercials, undated (Box 50)
  - "Speed" Riggs - Auctioneer, Sound Trax Inc., undated (Box 50)
  - Concert Spot: For Jim Hunt, undated (Box 50)
  - Thornburg Record on Crime #1, undated (Box 50)
  - Hunt -- Griffith Spots - 1. Selected Take: NC Democrat; 2. Selected Take: Social Security, undated (Box 50)
  - "Mailman," "S-158," "Big Spender", undated (Box 50)
  - Richard Petty Radio Endorsement / Gardner, undated (Box 50)
  - Voter Registration - Sheriff Baker; Baker for Hunt, undated (Box 50)
  - JHSEN-1037, "Young or Old", undated (Box 50)
  - JHSEN-1020, "September 9;" JHSEN-1021, "Fiscal Responsibility", undated (Box 50)
  - Death Squad :60 Radio, undated (Box 50)
  - WUNC: AIDS: Knowing about Health Care Workers; AIDS: Patient Testing and Informed Consent, undated (Box 50)
  - John Baker - Voter Registration, Pro-Hunt; Harvey Gantt - Voter Registration, Pro-Hunt, undated (Box 50)
  - Gardner: Testimonial Radio Ad, undated (Box 50)
  - Appalachia :60 Radio, undated (Box 50)
  - Unlabeled Maxell C90 Korea, undated (Box 50)
  - Report from United States Senator Jesse Helms, undated (Box 50)
  - Roberta Flack Concert :30, undated (Box 50)
  - JHSEN-1008, "Defense;" JHSEN-1009, "Defense;" JHSEN-1010, "Social Security;" JHSEN-1011, "Social Security", undated (Box 50)
  - Community College Trustees (Tape 2), undated (Box 50)
  - Cumberland Breakfast / Silver Lake / Catawba County High School; Davidson Young Democrats / Davidson High School, undated (Box 50)
  - Roberta Flack II :60, undated (Box 50)
  - Ronnie [illegible] about Jesse Agirculture & Defense Positive, undated (Box 50)
  - Congressional Club Ad #2, undated (Box 50)
  - Democrats for Jesse #2 :60, undated (Box 50)
  - JHSEN-1032, "Mailman;" JHSEN-1034, "S-158;" JHSEN-1033, "Big Spender", undated (Box 50)
  - JHSEN-1017, "Richardson-Preyer" :60, undated (Box 50)
  - Gardner Press Conference / Fair Sentencing Act - Hardee Ad, undated (Box 50)
  - Sam Perkins - Duke Recording Studios, undated (Box 50)
  - Ronnie Reagan calling Helms man with Courage :30 & :60, undated (Box 50)
  - Hunt -- Profiles Selected Takes: 1. Woman; 2. Education; 3. Senior; 4. Worker, undated (Box 50)
  - Strickland Radio Show, undated (Box 50)
  - Ronnie quoting Sam Ervin - defense, taxes, Helms positive, undated (Box 50)
  - Democratic Party Radio 5 60 second commercials, undated (Box 50)
  - Jim Hunt Six Spots: 1. Tax Fairness; 2. Tax Fair; 3. Education; 4. Environment; 5. Tobacco Tax; 6. Tobacco Tax, undated (Box 50)
  - Patterson & Governor Hunt's Conversation, undated (Box 50)
  - Fair Sentencing Act / Attack on Hunt, undated (Box 50)
  - Hunt/Gardner Comments Post Debate, undated (Box 50)
  - Gardner Education Press Conference, Charlotte SB, undated (Box 50)
  - Unlabelled, undated (Box 50)
  - Cabarrus County, Charlotte Motor Speedway; Union County, Bob Griffin's Home; Iredell County, Stamey's Farm, undated (Box 50)
  - Sampler of Helms Ads, undated (Box 50)
  - Governor Jim Hunt proclaimed April 13. 1981 as Nathan Yelton Day in honor if Yelton's 80th Birthday and 50 nyears in state service, undated (Box 50)
  - Positive #2 - Helms Balanced Budget, undated (Box 50)
  - Helms for Senate, Schools and UNCHEW, undated (Box 50)
  - Helms for Senate / Positive #1 5/23-5/27, undated (Box 50)
  - Asheville (Ind. Development Council) / Shelby (Board of Realtors) / Caswell Hunt Songs, undated (Box 50)
  - Crime Press Conference - 6/18, undated (Box 50)
  - Reading Press Conference (June 8), undated (Box 50)
  - Greenville - Wash. - New bern, undated (Box 50)
  - Economic Outlook - Harlan Boyles (1 of 2), undated (Box 50)
  - Economic Outlook - Harlan Boyles (2 of 2), undated (Box 50)
  - Private/Public Partnerships - Bev Perdue (1 of 2), undated (Box 50)
  - Private/Public Partnerships - Bev Perdue (2 of 2), undated (Box 50)
- Photographs, 1991-1992 and undated
  The series contains photographs, contact sheets, negatives, and slides. The images include official portraits of Hunt, official photographs from campaign events, and a small number of candid photos of Hunt taken by friends and supporters. Also included are documents detailing the provenance of some of the photographs.
  - Photographs: Hunt at Mount Mitchell, 1991 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Black & White Contact Sheets (1 of 2), 1992 February (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Black & White Contact Sheets (2 of 2), 1992 February (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Hunt in Classroom, 1992 April (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - Black & White Contact Sheets: Hunt with supporters, 1992 October (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Black & White Photographs: Hunt with supporters, 1992 October (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Color Photographs: Hunt at Democratic National Convention, candid, 1992 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Black & White Photographs: Hunt portraits, 1992 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Color Photographs: Hunt at the Science House, [1992?] (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Black & White Contact Sheets: Candid, undated (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Black & White Contact Sheets: Portrait, undated (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Color Slides by Will & Demi McIntyre, undated (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Photographs: Candid, undated (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Color Photographs: Hunt portaits, undated (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Photographs: Hunt, candid, undated (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Photographs and Brochures: Jim Gardner, Lacy Thornburg, undated (Box 51, Folder 15)
- Documents, 1971-1972, 1977-1996, and undated
  This series contains a variety of documents relating to Hunt's campaigns, including correspondence, clippings, ad slicks, position papers, and brochures. Included are materials produced by Hunt himself as well as materials from various campaign employees. Some of the materials document the audiovisual material in Series 1, Series 2, and Series 3.
  - Home Federal Loan materials - Gardner, 1971-1972, 1979, 1988, 1992 (Box 57, Folder 23)
  - Clippings: Hunt for Governor, 1975 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Hunt News Clippings, 1977-1984 (Box 57, Folder 24)
  - News Clippings, 1982-1992 (Box 57, Folder 25)
  - Clippings: Education, 1983-1990 (Box 59, Folder 20)
  - Use of State airplane, 1984 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - "Jim Hunt for Senate" campaign packet, 1984 (Box 59, Folder 17)
  - Clippings: Helms vs. Hunt, 1984-1989 (Box 59, Folder 21)
  - Cue Sheets (1 of 2), 1984 (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Cue Sheets (2 of 2), 1984 (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - News Clippings - Hunt, 1984 (Box 57, Folder 30)
  - Clippings: Hunt as Attorney, 1985 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Clippings: Martin vs. Hunt, 1987 June (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Paroles, 1987, 1992 (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Clippings: Pro-Hunt Editorials, 1987-1991 (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - Clippings: Governor power/authority, 1988 August (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Jim Gardner on Abortion, 1988, 1992 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Clippings (1 of 3), 1988-1992 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Clippings (2 of 3), 1988-1992 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Clippings (3 of 3), 1988-1992 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Clippings: Political, 1988-1991 (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - Clippings: Hunt for Senate 1992, 1988-1989 (Box 59, Folder 23)
  - Clippings: Hunt for Dukakis, 1988 (Box 59, Folder 24)
  - Clippings: Anti-Hunt editorials, 1989-1991 (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Clippings: Economic development, 1989-1991 (Box 59, Folder 16)
  - Clippings: Campaign '92, 1989-1991 (Box 59, Folder 22)
  - Vance-Aycock advertisement, 1991 August (Box 52, Folder 18)
  - Direct Mail 02, 1991 October 2 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Announcement Letter, 1991 October 3 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Direct Mail 03 - Jordan, 1991 November 15 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - State Employees Newsletter adverstisement, 1991-1992 (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - Public School Forum of North Carolina's World Class Schools Forum, 1991 December-1992 January (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Direct Mail 04, 1991 December-1992 January (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Telemarketing Letters, 1991 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Hunt Grams, 1991-1992 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1991 (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - Campaign themes, 1991 (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - Clippings: Community colleges, 1991 (Box 59, Folder 18)
  - Clippings: Hunt associates, 1991 (Box 59, Folder 19)
  - News Clippings - Prisons and Parole, 1991-1992 (Box 57, Folder 27)
  - Direct Mail 05, 1992 January 3 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Primary Brochure, 1992 January-March (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - State Employees Brochure, 1992 January (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Teachers Brochure, 1992 January (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Photo Releases, 1992 January-March (Box 57, Folder 19)
  - Clippings: Candidates, 1992 January-May (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People, Greensboro Branch Advertisement, 1992 February-March (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - University of North Carolina Center for Public Television Debate Format Correspondence, 1992 February-April (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Snapshots - photocopies of contact sheets, 1992 February (Box 57, Folder 20)
  - Clippings: Education, 1992 March 1-7 (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Clippings: Candidates, 1992 March 13-22 (Box 58, Folder 20)
  - Clippings: Education, 1992 March 8-14 (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - Clippings: Education, 1992 March 22-28 (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Clippings: Education, 1992 March 29-April 4 (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - Clippings: Candidates, 1992 March 29-April 4 (Box 58, Folder 19)
  - Clippings: Candidates, 1992 March 29-April 4 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Clippings: Candidates, 1992 March 29-April 4 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Durham Committee on the Affairs of Black People Advertsement, 1992 March-Aprll (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Garner Road YMCA Advertisement, 1992 March-Aprll (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Raleigh-Apex Branch of the National Association for the Advancement of Colored People, 1992 March (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Winston-Salem Branch of the National Association for the Advancement of Colored People Advertisement, 1992 March (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Democratic Party Advertisement for Jefferson-Jackson Dinner, 1992 March (Box 52, Folder 20)
  - Vision Brochure Printing Information, 1992 March (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Arts Advocates of North Carolina Forum, 1992 March-Aprll (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Young Democrats of North Carolina Gubernatorial Candidates Forum, 1992 March-Aprll (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Hunt Financial Disclosures (1 of 2), 1992 March-Aprll (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Hunt Financial Disclosures (2 of 2), 1992 March-Aprll (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Direct Mail 06, 1992 March (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Jim Hunt Photo Posters, 1992 April 1 (Flatbox 64)
  - Clippings: Education, 1992 April 5-11 (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - Clippings: Candidates (1 of 2), 1992 April 5-11 (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - Clippings: Candidates (2 of 2), 1992 April 5-11 (Box 58, Folder 21)
  - Clippings: Education, 1992 April 12-18 (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Clippings: Candidates, 1992 April 12-18 (Box 58, Folder 17)
  - Clippings: Candidates, 1992 April 12-18 (Box 58, Folder 22)
  - Memorandum - Advertising Materials, 1992 April 17 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Clippings: Education, 1992 April 19-25 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Clippings: Candidates, 1992 April 19-25 (Box 58, Folder 18)
  - Clippings: Candidates, 1992 April 26-May 2 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - North Carolina Black Leadership Caucus Annual Conference Advertisement, 1992 April (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - "Challenge" 60 second television advertisement transcript, 1992 April (Box 52, Folder 23)
  - JH-110: "Education 2" 30 second television advertisement transcript, 1992 April (Box 52, Folder 26)
  - North Carolina Association of Independent College and Universities Forum, 1992 April (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - WTVD Debate, 1992 April (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence - Photographers, 1992 April (Box 57, Folder 18)
  - Clippings: Candidates, 1992 May 3-9 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Clippings: Candidates, 1992 May 17-23 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Charlotte Observer Debate, 1992 May (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - North Carolina Alliance of Community Financial Institutions Forum Speech, 1992 May (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Jim Gardner Advertisement: "Business Leaders", 1992 May (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Greer, Margolis, Mitchell, Burns & Associates, Inc.: Personal Releases, 1992 May (Box 56, Folder 26)
  - Short Brochure and Palm Card, 1992 June (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Remarks at North Carolina Bar Association annual meeting, 1992 June (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Conference Call Memos, 1992 June-September (Box 56, Folder 32)
  - North Carolina Division of Motor Vehicles Enforcement Section Brochure, 1990 June (Box 57, Folder 21)
  - Press Clips Log (Video Clips), 1992 June-September (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - North Carolina Democratic Women's Club Convention Advertisement, 1992 July-August (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Sons of Confederate Veterans letter, 1992 July-August (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Debate Preparation, 1992 July-October (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - Endorsements, 1992 July-September (Box 53, Folder 18)
  - Candidates Forum on Child Health, 1992 July-August (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Citizens Forum (Winston-Salem), 1992 July (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Jim Gardner Advertisements: Biography, Business, 1992 July (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Jim Gardner Advertisement: "Crime", 1992 July (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Jim Gardner Ad Buys, 1992 July-October (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - Jim Gardner Advertisements: Education Bureaucracy, 1992 July (Box 55, Folder 17)
  - Architect's Letter, 1992 July (Box 55, Folder 20)
  - Hunt Letter to High Point Furniture Dealers, 1992 July (Box 55, Folder 21)
  - Health Care and Human Services Position Papers, 1992 July (Box 55, Folder 22)
  - Hunt Televison Advertisement: JH-110, "Education 2", 1992 August 18 (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - Hunt Radio Advertisement Script: "Reader", 1992 August 24 (Box 56, Folder 20)
  - Hunt Television Advertisement: "Again" (Tax Response #1), 1992 August 27 (Box 56, Folder 27)
  - Agriculture Testimonials, 1992 August (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Eduction Bureaucracy Response, radio advertisement, 1992 August (Box 52, Folder 21)
  - "Again" 30 second television advertisement transcript, 1992 August (Box 52, Folder 25)
  - Hunt Television Advertisement Script: "Plan 3", 1992 September 2 (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Hunt Television Advertisement: JH-115, "Truth" (Tax Response #1), 1992 September 10 (Box 56, Folder 28)
  - Hunt Television Advertisement: "Agenda for Action", 1992 September 22 (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - Action Agenda television advertisement, "Plan 3," 60 seconds, 1992 September (Box 52, Folder 22)
  - Economic Development and Jobs, 30 second television advertisement, 1992 September (Box 52, Folder 24)
  - Jeffreys and Heatherly book, Jim Gardner: A Question of Character, 1992 September (Box 53, Folder 19)
  - Radio and Television Spots, Scripts and Correspondence, 1992 September-October (Box 53, Folder 22)
  - Jim Gardner Radio Advertisement Script, Education Attack, 1992 September (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Jim Gardner Advertisement: Fair Sentencing Act, 1992 September (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - Absentee Voter Cards, 1992 September (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Hunt Television Advertisement Script: "Fair", 1992 September 30 (Box 56, Folder 21)
  - Eastern North Carolina Farmers Event Ad Copy, 1992 September (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Hunt Television Advertisement Script: "Crime - Plan", 1992 October 2 (Box 56, Folder 22)
  - Hunt Television Advertisement: Gardner Business, 1992 October 6 (Box 56, Folder 23)
  - Hunt Television Advertisement Script: "Family", 1992 October 7 (Box 56, Folder 16)
  - Hunt Television Advertisement Scripts: "Town Hall," "Teacher", 1992 October 7 (Box 56, Folder 19)
  - Hunt Radio Advertisement: "Trust" (ThermalKEM Response), 1992 October 8 (Box 56, Folder 29)
  - Hunt Television Advertisement: Gardner Business #2, 1992 October 15 (Box 56, Folder 24)
  - Hunt - Charlie Gaddy Show, 1992 October 21 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - 27 Ayu, 1992 October 22 (Box 56, Folder 25)
  - Hunt Television Advertisement: "Attend", 1992 October 23 (Box 56, Folder 30)
  - Hunt Television Advertisement Script: Agenda-Economic-Office, 1992 October 26 (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Hunt Television Advertisement Script: "Eastern", 1992 October 26 (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - Hunt Advertisement Scripts: "Difference" (Radio), "Dirt" (Television), "Final" (Television), 1992 October 30 (Box 56, Folder 17)
  - Gardner Radio Advertisement Script: Eavesdropping, 1992 October 30 (Box 56, Folder 18)
  - Democratic Party of North Carolina Election Night Victory Celebration, 1992 October-November (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Newspaper Editorials, 1992 October (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Newspaper Profiles, 1992 October (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Lacy H. Thornburg Letter Challenging Hunt to Debate, 1991 October (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Young Democrats of North Carolina Forum, Vance-Aycock, 1992 October (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Crime Pocket Card, 1992 October (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Jim Gardner and Bailey Marketing, 1992 October (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Jim Gardner Advertisment, Business Defense, Lobbyist, 1992 October (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Jim Gardner Radio Advertisement Script: Attack on Hunt's Record as Governor, 1992 October (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - Hunt Print Advertisement: State Employees/Others, 1992 October 31 (Box 56, Folder 31)
  - Hunt Victory Statement, 1992 November 3 (Box 57, Folder 16)
  - Hunt Thank You Letters, 1992 November 10 (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - Newspaper Advertisement (Last Days), 1992 November (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Newspaper Coverage of Election Night, 1992 November (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - Carolina Clipping Service: Election Results, 1992 November (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Carolina Clipping Service: Precinct Results, 1992 November (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Carolina Clipping Service: Election Results Editorials, 1992 November (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Carolina Clipping Service: Hunt Transition, Election Results, 1992 November (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Carolina Clipping Service: Election Analysis, 1992 November-December (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Carolina Clipping Service: Schools, Election Results, 1992 November-December (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Carolina Clipping Service: Inauguration, 1992 December (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Carolina Clipping Service: Guns, 1992 December (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Carolina Clipping Service: Family Leave, Election Results, 1992 December (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Newspaper Insert, Agriculture, 1992 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Baptist Ministers Conference of Winston-Salem, North Carolina and Vicinity Advertisement, 1992 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - College Students Flyer, 1992 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - The State Employee Reporter advertisement, 1992 (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Vance-Aycock Dinner ad copy, 1992 (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - Young Democrats of Mecklenburg County advertisement, 1992 (Box 52, Folder 19)